<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DocDock Documentation</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DocDock Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/hackthebox/challenges/bloodhound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hackthebox/challenges/bloodhound/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BloodHound Neo4j</title>
      <link>/tools/bloodhound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/bloodhound/</guid>
      <description>TAKE A SNAPSHOT BEFORE ATTEMPTING THIS.
I would highly recommend installing Neo4j using the repository. Neo4j is a database for bloodhound API. I had a couple of issues installing this. had some issues with multiple versions of Java running. currently, neo4k only runs on Java 8 kali currently comes with 11.x. need to tell java to use the legacy version. Next, need to add the repository to download neo4j.
##### echo &amp;quot;deb http://httpredir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ChickenPwny</title>
      <link>/_header/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/_header/</guid>
      <description> ChickenPwny </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTP</title>
      <link>/tools/ftp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/ftp/</guid>
      <description>File transfer protocol is a terrible service and you should never run it without some kind of protection in front of it. I&amp;rsquo;ve bumped into quite a few boxes running FTP. I often forget all the commands you can run with ftp.
mget * download everything in the directory get download file / documents put upload file / documents nmap (maybe even in intereactive mode)  SSHFS &amp;amp; SFTP
SSHFS is built on SFTP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo/Github/Power</title>
      <link>/hackthebox/github/hugopowershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hackthebox/github/hugopowershell/</guid>
      <description>POWERSHELL Overview, how to install Hugo and how to set up the web pages using GitHub as repository in a WINDOWS environment. Since most of the commands have a Linux counterpart you could follow.
First off id like to say I wish there was a way to do this with less command line. I initially tried setting it up on GITLAB but I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the material I need to do within windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Manager Down</title>
      <link>/network-manager-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/network-manager-down/</guid>
      <description>The weirdest glitch bug I&amp;rsquo;ve ever experienced I am not sure I how I deleted the icon but it disappeared I could no longer access the network manager. Well fix the problem and see how to get to the internet without the network manager.
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if completely removing the network manager is required but i purged it out.
 sudo apt-get purge network-manager  To gain internet access even though the network manager is down and isn&amp;rsquo;t connected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SqlMap</title>
      <link>/tools/webapp/sqlmap/sqlmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/webapp/sqlmap/sqlmap/</guid>
      <description>SqlMap automates finding sql-injection it can use GET or POST request. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty neat.
In burp right click select copy to file, this will test for sql injection. pretty cool wasn&amp;rsquo;t aware it would test all the parameters. sqlmap &amp;ndash;batch -r login.req
sqlmap --batch -u &amp;quot;http://os.htb/users/admin*&amp;quot; --level 5 --risk 3 -u url also for get request --batch run default yes --* = the parameter to fuzz --dump , --dump-all dumping sqldb to a localfile in /  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>