<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on Pwny_Sec</title>
    <link>/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on Pwny_Sec</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BloodHound Neo4j</title>
      <link>/tools/bloodhound/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/bloodhound/</guid>
      <description>TAKE A SNAPSHOT BEFORE ATTEMPTING THIS.
I would highly recommend installing Neo4j using the repository. Neo4j is a database for bloodhound API. I had a couple of issues installing this. had some issues with multiple versions of Java running. currently, neo4k only runs on Java 8 kali currently comes with 11.x. need to tell java to use the legacy version. Next, need to add the repository to download neo4j.
##### echo &amp;quot;deb http://httpredir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ChiselTunnel</title>
      <link>/tools/chisel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/chisel/</guid>
      <description>Chisel SERVER
./Chisel server -p 8000 -reverse -v -reverse the connection this is important -v verbose -p port  Chisel.exe CLIENT
c.exe client 10.10.15.254:8000 R:127.0.0.1:8001:localhost:8081	 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FTP</title>
      <link>/tools/ftp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/ftp/</guid>
      <description>File transfer protocol is a terrible service and you should never run it without some kind of protection in front of it. I&amp;rsquo;ve bumped into quite a few boxes running FTP. I often forget all the commands you can run with ftp.
https://slacksite.com/other/ftp.html
mget * download everything in the directory get download file / documents put upload file / documents nmap (maybe even in intereactive mode)  SSHFS &amp;amp; SFTP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nmap</title>
      <link>/tools/nmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/nmap/</guid>
      <description>tcp connect its quicker and might discover some hidden services
nmap -sT -p- -Pn -T5 nmap/initial ip_addr  Next move to targeted nmap scans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMB</title>
      <link>/tools/smb/smb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tools/smb/smb/</guid>
      <description>Mounting smb shares linux
You may get an error, this means that the supporting programs aren&amp;rsquo;t there.
sudo apt install cifs-utils -y sudo apt install nfs-common  Error Message
bad option; for several filesystems (e.g. nfs, cifs) you might need a /sbin/mount.&amp;lt;type&amp;gt; helper program.  Example
mount -o user=REPLACE &#39;//ip_addr/share&#39; /mnt/share  +++
SMBCLIENT
Usage: smbclient service &amp;lt;password&amp;gt; -R, --name-resolve=NAME-RESOLVE-ORDER Use these name resolution services only -M, --message=HOST Send message -I, --ip-address=IP Use this IP to connect to -E, --stderr Write messages to stderr instead of stdout -L, --list=HOST Get a list of shares available on a host -m, --max-protocol=LEVEL Set the max protocol level -T, --tar=&amp;lt;c|x&amp;gt;IXFqgbNan Command line tar -D, --directory=DIR Start from directory -c, --command=STRING Execute semicolon separated commands -b, --send-buffer=BYTES Changes the transmit/send buffer -t, --timeout=SECONDS Changes the per-operation timeout -p, --port=PORT Port to connect to -g, --grepable Produce grepable output -q, --quiet Suppress help message -B, --browse Browse SMB servers using DNS Help options: -?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>